{
    "subject": "resource/Chinese_Pavilion_at_Drottningholm",
    "predicate": "property/location",
    "object": "resource/Eker\u00f6_Municipality",
    "human_readable": "The Chinese Pavilion at Drottningholm is located in Eker\u00f6 Municipality.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9854674339294434,
            "question": "Is the Chinese Pavilion at Drottningholm situated within a municipality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9821946024894714,
            "question": "Where is the Chinese Pavilion at Drottningholm located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9588963985443115,
            "question": "What municipality is home to the Chinese Pavilion at Drottningholm?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9395466446876526,
            "question": "In what country would you find the Chinese Pavilion at Drottningholm?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8954105377197266,
            "question": "What architectural style might be found in the Chinese Pavilion at Drottningholm?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8063820600509644,
            "question": "Why might someone visit the Chinese Pavilion at Drottningholm?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8049726486206055,
            "question": "Is there any historical significance associated with the Chinese Pavilion at Drottningholm?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7804974913597107,
            "question": "Where would you go to learn more about the history of the Chinese Pavilion at Drottningholm?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6359744668006897,
            "question": "What is the name of the structure located in Eker\u00f6 Municipality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.445424348115921,
            "question": "Can you tell me about a notable building in Eker\u00f6 Municipality?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Chinese Pavilion at Drottningholm is located in Eker\u00f6 Municipality.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3428_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the structure located in Eker\u00f6 Municipality?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3428_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where would you go to learn more about the history of the Chinese Pavilion at Drottningholm?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3428_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any historical significance associated with the Chinese Pavilion at Drottningholm?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3428_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3428_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3428_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3428_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3428_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3428_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3428_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3428_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3428_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3428_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3428_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the location of the Chinese Pavilion, which is situated in Drottningholm, Eker\u00f6 Municipality, Stockholm County, Sweden. This confirms that the statement \"The Chinese Pavilion at Drottningholm is located in Eker\u00f6 Municipality\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}